quttera.com 2019-12-21

# FREE Online Website Malware Scanner | Website Security Monitoring & Malware Removal | Quttera

**Date of last revision: May 24, 2018**

This Privacy Policy describes how Quttera LTD use, collect and share information in connection with your use of our websites (www.quttera.com, https://blog.quttera.com/, https://threatsign.com, https://malwaredecoder.com/, https://helpdesk.quttera.com/), products, services and applications. This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") does not apply to information our clients may process when using our Services.

Quttera LTD ("we" or "us") may collect and receive information about users of our Services ("users," "you," or "your") from different sources, including: (i) data you provide through your user (your "Account") if you sign up for the Services; (ii) your use of the products and/or Services; and (iii) from third-party websites, services, and partners. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to ensure you are fully informed. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy or Quttera LTD data collection, use, and disclosure practices, please contact us at contactus@quttera.com. 

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

### Anonymous data collection

You can visit our websites without disclosing your identity. No personal data is collected with regards to this kind of visits. The information about your visits will only be analysed for the statistical purposes, that cannot be traced back to you, and in order to improve our offering.

### Account Registration

When you sign up for an Account, we will collect your contact information, including items such as name, email address, company name, address, and telephone number. When you refer a friend to our Services, we may also collect your friend's email address so that we may send a referral or promotional code to sign up for our Services.

### Collection and processing when using our helpdesk system

When the helpdesk system is used we collect personal data (information that can be used to identify a specific or determinable natural person) only to the extent in which the individual provides it. We only use your email address and name for dealing with your query.

### Collection, processing, and use of personal data

We collect personal data (information that can be used to identify a specific or determinable natural person) only to the degree in which the individual provides it. Your personal data is processed and used for fulfilling and transacting your order and for dealing with your queries.

Following the complete fulfillment of your order, all personal data is stored under observance of tax and commercial law retention periods and is then deleted on expiry of that period, unless you have provided consent to further processing and use.

If you subscribe to our services, we may collect credit card or additional payment information from you. However, we do not store any of this payment information or process any of your payments on our servers. We use a third-party payment service known as 'BlueSnap'. Therefore, any information regarding your payment processing and security must be verified in BlueSnap's own Terms of Service Agreement: <https://home.bluesnap.com/terms-and-conditions/> and Privacy Policy: <https://home.bluesnap.com/privacy-policy/>

The payment processor 'BlueSnap' may also provide us with information about your account details, payment information and your order status, such as your name, credit card type, expiration date, and the last four digits of your credit card number. We may use this information for accounting, to satisfy a legal process or government request, for customer claim resolutions, and customer support. We may also request and receive any payment history between the user and Quttera LTD.

We offer an option to pay for our services using PayPal. When you use PayPal's website to make a payment to us, you are subject to PayPal's Privacy Policy: <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>. We may use the information you have provided by PayPal for accounting, to satisfy a legal process or government request, for customer claim resolutions, and customer support.

### Collection and use of email address for sending newsletters

We will use your email address solely for sending newsletters for our own specific purposes, where you have explicitly allowed this. By providing your consent to receive the newsletter you recognize the following: 

#### Information on the newsletter:

The newsletter appears regularly and contains security tips, IT and web security news, cybersecurity and information on current Quttera LTD promotions.

You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time by using the corresponding link in the newsletter or by contacting us at **support@quttera.com**. Your email address will then be deleted from the distribution list.

### Use of email address for sending advertising

We may use your email address exclusively for our own promotional purposes to offer our own products and/or services. You can withdraw your consent to this usage at any time and we will remove your email address from the distribution list. To do so, you can use the corresponding link in the newsletter. Alternatively, you can communicate this retraction using any other channel, not just via email. Please note, it must reach us to take effect. No transmission costs shall arise from doing so other than those in accordance with basic rates.

### Forwarding personal data

We will not send your data to third parties without your express consent. The only exceptions to this are our service partners, whom we require for fulfilling the contractual relationship.

## HOW WE USE INFORMATION – Summary

We use the data we collect in various ways, including to:

  * Provide, operate, improve and maintain our Services and Products;
  * Improve, personalize, and expand our Services and Products;
  * Understand and analyze how you use our Services and Products;
  * Develop new products, services, features, and functionality;
  * Process your transactions and manage your subscriptions;
  * Communicate with you both directly or through one of our partners, including for customer support or service, for marketing and promotional purposes and to provide you with updates and other information relating to the Service;
  * Send you text messages and push notifications;
  * Find and prevent fraud; and
  * For compliance with law and procedures purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service, resolution of billing disputes, or other legal rights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency.

## HOW WE USE INFORMATION – Details

### Cookies

Our websites use cookies in various places. Cookies are pieces of information in the form of small text files that are placed on your computer and saved by your browser. They are used to improve our services and make them more user-friendly, effective and secure. Also, cookies enable our systems to identify your browser and offer you our services. Cookies do not contain any personal data.

### Use of the Google Inc. remarketing or "Similar Audiences" function

The provider uses the Google Inc. ("Google") remarketing or "Similar Audiences" function on the website. The provider can use this function to address visitors to the website with targeted advertising, by switching on display advertising related to the interests of users of the provider's website when they visit other websites in the Google Display Network. Google uses cookies to run an analysis of website usage, which forms the basis for generating interest-related display advertising. Google does so by storing a small file with a sequence of numbers in the browsers of visitors to the website. This number is used to capture visits to the website and anonymous data on the use of the website. No personal data regarding visitors to the website is stored. If you subsequently visit another website on the Google Display Network, you are shown advertising displays that most probably concern product and information areas previously visited.

You can permanently disable the use of cookies by Google by following the link below and downloading and installing the plug-in provided: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996>

Alternatively, you can disable the use of cookies by third-party providers by going to the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ and implementing the additional information given there on opting out.

You can find additional information on Google remarketing and the Google data protection declaration at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

### Use of Google Adwords Conversion Tracking

We use the Google AdWords online advertising program and Conversion Tracking as part of Google AdWords. Google Conversion Tracking is an analysis service offered by Google Inc. 

If you click on advertising switched on by Google, a Conversion Tracking cookie is deposited on your computer. These cookies have restricted validity, do not contain personal data and therefore are not used for identifying individuals.

If you visit certain pages on our website and the cookie has not yet expired, Google and we can detect that you have clicked on the advert and been forwarded to this page.

Every Google AdWords customer has a different cookie. Hence there is no possibility of cookies being traced back via the websites of AdWords customers.

The information obtained using the conversion cookie is used to generate conversion statistics for AdWords customers that are critical for conversion tracking. In this way, the customers learn the total number of users that have clicked on the advert and have been forwarded to a page provided with a Conversion Tracking tag. However, they do not receive any information that can be used for personally identifying users.

If you do not wish to participate in tracking, you can retract your consent for this usage by preventing the installation of cookies via a corresponding setting in your browser software (disabling option). You will then be excluded from the Conversion Tracking statistics.

You can find additional information and the Google data protection declaration at <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

### Use of Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service offered by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies – text files that are stored on your computer and enable analysis of the way you are using the website. The data captured via the cookie regarding your use of this website is generally forwarded to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, if IP anonymization has been enabled on this website, your IP address is first abbreviated by Google within member states of the European Union or in other states party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. The full IP address is only transferred to a Google server in the USA and abbreviated there in exceptional cases. At the request of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to analyze your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide additional services connected with the use of the website and the Internet on the part of the website operator. The IP address communicated by your browser in the context of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data. You can block the storage of cookies using an appropriate setting in your browser software. However, we advise you that, if you do so, you may not be able to use all the functions on this website to their full extent. Furthermore, you can prevent the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) from being captured and processed by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in provided in the following link <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

This website also uses Google Analytics reports on demographic characteristics in which data on interest-related advertising from Google and visitor data from third-party providers (e.g., age, gender, and interests) are used. This data cannot be traced back to a specific individual and can be disabled at any time via the display settings: <https://adssettings.google.com/anonymous?hl=en>

### Use of Facebook plug-ins

Plug-ins for the social network facebook.com are used on this website. These are operated by Facebook Inc.("Facebook").

If you access pages on our website provided with such a plug-in, a connection with the Facebook servers will be established and the plug-in displayed on the web page by communicating with your browser. In this way information is sent to the Facebook servers on which of our web pages you have visited. If you are logged into Facebook when this happens, Facebook will allocate this information to your personal Facebook user account. If you use the plug-in functions (e.g. click on the "Like" button, post a comment), this information is also allocated to your Facebook account. You can only prevent this by logging out before using the plug-in.

You can find more information on how Facebook acquires and uses data, your rights in this matter and the options for protecting your privacy in the Facebook data protection information.

### Use of Facebook Pixel

Our website measures conversions using visitor action pixels from Facebook.

These allow the behavior of site visitors to be tracked after they click on a Facebook ad to reach the provider's website. This allows an analysis of the effectiveness of Facebook advertisements for statistical and market research purposes and their future optimization.

The data collected is anonymous to us as operators of this website and we cannot use it to draw any conclusions about our users' identities. However, the data are stored and processed by Facebook, which may make a connection to your Facebook profile and which may use the data for its own advertising purposes, as stipulated in the Facebook privacy policy. This will allow Facebook to display ads both on Facebook and on third-party sites. We have no control over how this data is used.

Check out Facebook's privacy policy to learn more about protecting your privacy: : <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>.

You can also deactivate the custom audiences remarketing feature in the Ads Settings section at <https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen>. You will first need to log into Facebook.

If you do not have a Facebook account, you can opt out of usage-based advertising from Facebook on the website of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance: <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/de/praferenzmanagement/>.

### Use of the Google +1 button

The +1 button for the Google Plus social network operated by Google Inc is used on these web pages. If you access a page on our website bearing the +1 button, a connection with the Google servers in the USA will be established and the button will be displayed on the web page by communicating with your browser. In doing so, your IP address and information on which of our web pages you have visited are submitted to the Google servers. This is regardless of whether you have registered or logged in with Google Plus. Submission takes place even with users who are not registered or logged in. The +1 button is not used to capture information on where you go on the Internet. Google does not permanently log your browser behavior when a +1 button is displayed and does not analyze your visit to a page with a +1 button in any other way. Google stores data concerning your visit for around 14 days for system maintenance and error removal purposes. However, this data is not structured according to individual profiles, user names or URLs and is also not forwarded to us.

Furthermore, if you are a member of Google Plus and are logged in to Google Plus during the time you are using the plug-in, the information acquired regarding your visit to website is linked to your Google Plus account and disclosed to other users. Also, information about you regarding interactions that are possible using the various Google plug-ins is collected, sent to Google and stored. You can find an overview of the various types of Google plug-ins here: <https://developers.google.com/+/web/>

If you have made your profile publicly accessible in the Google Plus settings, your +1 may be displayed by Google as information, together with your profile name and photo, in Google services such as search results, or in your Google profile, or in other locations on websites and in display advertisements on the Internet. If you do not want Google to allocate the data acquired directly to your Google Plus profile, you will need to log out of Google Plus before visiting our site.

You can find more information on how Google acquires and uses data, your rights in this matter and the options for protecting your privacy in the Google data protection information: <https://developers.google.com/+/web/+1button/>

You also have the option of preventing Google plug-ins from loading by installing appropriate add-ons in your browser.

### Use of Twitter plug-ins

The functions of the Twitter service are integrated into our website. Twitter is a social media portal owned by Twitter Inc.

We use Twitter plug-ins. If you access a corresponding website that contains such a plug-in, data will be exchanged with Twitter servers located in the USA. Also, information about you regarding interactions that are possible using the various Twitter plug-ins is collected, sent to Twitter and stored.

Furthermore, if you are a member of Twitter and are logged in to Twitter during the time you are using the plug-in, the information acquired regarding your visit to the website is linked to your Twitter account and disclosed to other users.

If you do not want Twitter to link the information to the data in your Twitter account and merge it, you will need to log out of Twitter before visiting our website. You can find more information on how Twitter acquires and uses data at <https://twitter.com/en/privacy>

### Use of Hotjar

We use Hotjar in order to better understand our users' needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don't like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies (<https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/cookie-information>) and other technologies to collect data on our users' behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar's privacy policy by clicking on this link.

You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar's storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar's use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this opt-out link: <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out>

### Use of Youtube cookies

We use the YouTube, LLC (by Google Inc) AdWords online advertising program and Conversion Tracking as part of Google AdWords. Google Conversion Tracking is an analysis service offered by Google Inc. You can find additional information and the Google data protection declaration at <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out>

### Use of Google Tag Manager

We use the Google Tag Manager to place and control the web page tags through a user interface. It does not collect personal data. It allows triggering of other tags but does not access the data acquired by them.

<https://www.google.com/analytics/tag-manager/use-policy/>

### Use of Google Optimize

We use Google Optimize to run tests measuring the effects of various changes to a website (e.g. different labels, controls, input fields, etc.) which is also known as "A/B tests". This will help us to identify the areas for improvement in the user experience and interface of website.

Optimize Terms of Service (<https://support.google.com/optimize/answer/6230273>) in addition to Google's Privacy Policy (<https://policies.google.com/privacy/update?hl=en)>

### Use of LinkedIn

We allow visitors to access our company page on LinkedIn. For more information please visit LinkedIn's privacy policy: <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy> and Cookie Policy: <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie_policy>

## HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION

We may share the data that we collect in different ways, including the following: 

### Vendors and Service Providers

We may share information with third-party vendors, service providers, affiliates, subsidiaries or other parties that provide services on our behalf or help us to provide our Services. Such vendors may include payment processing platforms, billing companies, analytics service providers, cloud computing platforms, and website infrastructure management providers. We are working only with trusted external service providers which we carefully select to meet our data protection and security standards. We also sign contracts with such providers to ensure they employ appropriate data protection and security measures.

We may use the following third-party service providers named below to process and store data:

  * Mailchimp (The Rocket Science Group, LLC), which we use to manage subscriber lists, send newsletter emails, or other service related emails, to users who subscribed to receive them. Read their Privacy Policy: <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>
  * BlueSnap – payment platform, which we use to process payments and subscriptions to our services and products. Read their Privacy Policy: <https://home.bluesnap.com/privacy-policy/>
  * PayPal – payment platform, which we use to process payments and subscriptions to our services and products. Read their Privacy Policy: <https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

We may also use other third-party providers to receive services such as processing, storage and technical analysis of the data and services.

### Aggregate Information

Where legally permissible, we may collect, use and share information about users with our partners, that is aggregated and/or de-identified and and/or does not identify you.

### Advertising

We work with third-party advertising partners to deliver you ads that we think may be relevant to you. These advertising partners may employ their own cookies, pixel tags, and similar technologies on our Services, and they may otherwise gather or have access to information about you which they may collect over time and across different online services.

### Third-Party Partners

We may also share information about users with third-party partners to receive additional publicly available information about you.

### You Sign Up for Services Through a Referral

If you sign up for our Services through a referral from a friend, we may share information with your referrer to let them know that you used their referral to sign up for our Services.

### Analytics

We use analytics providers such as Google Analytics. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect non-identifying information. Google provides some additional privacy options regarding its Analytics cookies at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.

### Business Transfers

We may disclose the information and otherwise transfer it as a part of the corporate event transaction such as (acquisition, merger, sale of assets, and similar). The information may also be transferred to one or more third parties as one/ part of our business assets in the event of insolvency, receivership or bankruptcy.

### Comply with Regulatory, Legal Obligations and Similar Disclosures

We may also share information to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; (iv) respond to your requests; or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.

### With Your Consent

We may share information with your consent.

## SECURITY

Quttera LTD is committed to protecting your information. To do so, we employ a variety of security technologies as well as internal policies and measures designed to protect the data from the disclosure or an unauthorized access or use. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information. However, please be advised that the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

## DATA RETENTION

We retain various types of personal information we collect from you where there is an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, if such data is subject ti specific legal, tax, or accounting requirements or if this data is required to continue providing the Services to you).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, in cases where this is not possible (for example, when it has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

### ACCESS

If you are a registered user, you may access certain personal information associated with your Account by logging into our Services or emailing contactus@quttera.com. If you terminate your Account, we may store the activity on your Account prior to deletion but never and under any circumstance will it be accessible to the public. 

We may periodically store and/or archive the information you provide us as a backup processes according to backup processes conducted in the ordinary course of business for disaster recovery purposes. We may first need to take reasonable steps to verify your identity updating or removing your information. We may temporarily limit your ability to access and correct your information where such access and correction could: inhibit Quttera LTD ability to comply with a legal obligation; inhibit Quttera LTD ability to conduct investigation, make or defend legal claims; result in disclosure of personal information about a third party; or result in breach of a contract or disclosure of trade secrets or other proprietary business information belonging to Quttera LTD or a third party.

## CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

The Services we provide are not intended to be used by children, and children under 13 are prohibited from using our Services. Quttera LTD does not knowingly collect or store personal information from children. If you learn that a child has provided us with personal information in violation of this Privacy Policy, you can alert us at **contactus@quttera.com**.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may modify, review and revise this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. We will post changes to this Privacy Policy on our websites. In cases we materially change how we use or share personal data previously gathered from our users through our Services, we will notify you through our Services, by email, or other communication. 

## INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS

Quttera LTD is a global business. As such, we may transfer or disclose personal information to countries other than the country in which you initially provided the data. These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## DISCLOSURE, AMENDMENT, BLOCKING AND ERASURE OF DATA

At all times you have the right of free disclosure, amendment, blocking and deletion of your stored data. Please contact us whenever you need to at **contactus@quttera.com**.

You have a right to be informed of Personal Data processed by Quttera LTD, a right to rectification/correction, restriction of processing and deletion. You also have the right to receive from Quttera LTD a structured, common and machine-readable format of Personal Data you provided to us.

We can only identify you via your email address and we can only adhere to your request and provide information if we have Personal Data about you through you having contacted us directly and/or you are using our site and/or service. We cannot provide, rectify or delete any data that we store on behalf of our users or customers.

If you wish to exercise any of the rights as mentioned in this Privacy Policy and/or if you have questions or comments relating to the use of Personal Data you may contact Quttera’s LTD support team at **contactus@quttera.com**

You have the right to withdraw consent, if you have given us your consent to process your data, at any time and where relevant, without affecting the lawfulness of the processing that was carried out prior to withdrawing it. Whenever you withdraw consent, you acknowledge and accept that this may have a negative influence on the quality of the Quttera LTD Site and/or Services. You further agree that Quttera LTD shall not be held liable with respect to any loss and/or damage to your Personal Data if you choose to withdraw consent.

Where Personal Data is processed for the above purposes based on Quttera’s LTD legitimate interests, under the GDPR, you may object to such processing at any time. To do so please contact at **contactus@quttera.com**.

In addition, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority in your jurisdiction.

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

This website may contain external links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. Please note that we do not have any control over the other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns relating to this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at **contactus@quttera.com**.

### Blog: Magento Skimmer in Google Analytics Plugin

A credit card skimmer inserts a request for credit card information and sends the response to the attacker's site. Recently we found another variant on the same trick, using the Google Analytics Pro plugin.

### Blog: Finding and Stopping Malicious HTTP Redirection

If malicious redirects infiltrate a website, it's important to get rid of them. It's equally important to find and fix the vulnerabilities that allowed them and improve website protection.

### Blog: Quttera Web Application Firewall Statistics for 2018

In the period from July through December, Quttera Firewall handled 48,180,062 requests and blocked 617,074 attacks. The majority (62%) of the attacks originated from IP addresses in the United States.

* * *

* * *

© 2019 Quttera Ltd. All rights reserved.
